{"id": 73, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Ana", "Silva", "traveled", "from", "Barcelona", "to", "meet", "Professor", "Luis", "Gómez", "at", "the", "conference", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9875, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.7619, "duplication": 0.2381}, "quality_score": 0.8248}
{"id": 80, "tokens": ["The", "engineers", "at", "SpaceX", "tested", "their", "new", "rocket", "in", "Florida", "yesterday", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.7222, "duplication": 0.2778}, "quality_score": 0.8167}
{"id": 49, "tokens": ["Ada", "Lovelace", "pioneered", "computing", "while", "experimenting", "with", "analytical", "engines", "in", "Victorian", "England", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.6842, "duplication": 0.3158}, "quality_score": 0.8053}
{"id": 95, "tokens": ["Ada", "Liu", "gave", "a", "groundbreaking", "presentation", "in", "Cambridge", "last", "week", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.625, "duplication": 0.375}, "quality_score": 0.7875}
{"id": 33, "tokens": ["OpenAI", "opened", "a", "new", "research", "center", "in", "Toronto", "last", "month", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.5882, "duplication": 0.4118}, "quality_score": 0.7765}
{"id": 88, "tokens": ["The", "International", "Space", "Station", "completed", "its", "orbit", "over", "Sahara", "Desert", "yesterday", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.5882, "duplication": 0.4118}, "quality_score": 0.7765}
{"id": 13, "tokens": ["Renowned", "chef", "Gordon", "Ramsay", "opened", "a", "new", "restaurant", "in", "Tokyo", "last", "month", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.5789, "duplication": 0.4211}, "quality_score": 0.7737}
{"id": 82, "tokens": ["The", "CEO", "of", "Google", "announced", "a", "new", "data", "center", "in", "Dublin", "next", "month", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.5789, "duplication": 0.4211}, "quality_score": 0.7737}
{"id": 66, "tokens": ["The", "International", "Space", "Station", "orbits", "above", "the", "Sahara", "Desert", "every", "few", "minutes", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9846, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.5882, "duplication": 0.4118}, "quality_score": 0.7718}
{"id": 3, "tokens": ["Renowned", "chef", "Gordon", "Ramsay", "unveiled", "his", "new", "line", "of", "eco", "‑", "friendly", "cookware", "at", "the", "Sustainable", "Kitchen", "Expo", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.5714, "duplication": 0.4286}, "quality_score": 0.7714}
{"id": 4, "tokens": ["Ada", "Lovelace", "presented", "her", "new", "algorithm", "at", "the", "Quantum", "Computing", "Expo", "yesterday", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.5556, "duplication": 0.4444}, "quality_score": 0.7667}
{"id": 32, "tokens": ["Ada", "Lovelace", "presented", "her", "new", "algorithm", "at", "Google", "headquarters", "in", "Mountain", "View", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.5556, "duplication": 0.4444}, "quality_score": 0.7667}
{"id": 39, "tokens": ["Ada", "Lovelace", "unveiled", "her", "new", "algorithm", "at", "the", "tech", "symposium", "in", "London", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.5556, "duplication": 0.4444}, "quality_score": 0.7667}
{"id": 48, "tokens": ["Ada", "Lovelace", "presented", "her", "algorithm", "at", "the", "annual", "conference", "hosted", "by", "TechNova", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.5556, "duplication": 0.4444}, "quality_score": 0.7667}
{"id": 90, "tokens": ["Ada", "Lovelace", "presented", "her", "algorithm", "to", "the", "board", "of", "Google", "in", "London", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.5556, "duplication": 0.4444}, "quality_score": 0.7667}
{"id": 50, "tokens": ["Ada", "Lovelace", "unveiled", "the", "new", "QuantumAI", "platform", "at", "the", "conference", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9818, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.5625, "duplication": 0.4375}, "quality_score": 0.7633}
{"id": 41, "tokens": ["Ada", "Lovelace", "pioneered", "computing", "while", "discussing", "quantum", "algorithms", "at", "a", "symposium", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.5, "duplication": 0.5}, "quality_score": 0.75}
{"id": 14, "tokens": ["The", "headquarters", "of", "Google", "in", "Mountain", "View", "announced", "a", "new", "AI", "initiative", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.4706, "duplication": 0.5294}, "quality_score": 0.7412}
{"id": 71, "tokens": ["Renowned", "chef", "Gordon", "Ramsay", "unveiled", "his", "new", "vegan", "line", "today", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.4706, "duplication": 0.5294}, "quality_score": 0.7412}
{"id": 75, "tokens": ["The", "headquarters", "of", "OpenAI", "in", "San", "Francisco", "announced", "a", "new", "AI", "model", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.4706, "duplication": 0.5294}, "quality_score": 0.7412}
{"id": 68, "tokens": ["Renowned", "chef", "Gordon", "Ramsay", "announced", "his", "new", "line", "of", "plant", "-", "based", "cookware", "today", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.45, "duplication": 0.55}, "quality_score": 0.735}
{"id": 87, "tokens": ["Renowned", "chef", "Gordon", "Ramsay", "announced", "a", "new", "plant", "-", "based", "menu", "at", "his", "flagship", "restaurant", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.45, "duplication": 0.55}, "quality_score": 0.735}
{"id": 23, "tokens": ["The", "research", "team", "from", "GlobalTech", "Solutions", "presented", "their", "findings", "in", "Berlin", "last", "week", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.4118, "duplication": 0.5882}, "quality_score": 0.7235}
{"id": 9, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "delivered", "a", "lecture", "in", "Cairo", "about", "renewable", "energy", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9846, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.6842, "duplication": 0.3158}, "quality_score": 0.7206}
{"id": 38, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Sarah", "Connor", "arrived", "in", "Nairobi", "for", "the", "international", "health", "summit", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9846, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.6842, "duplication": 0.3158}, "quality_score": 0.7206}
{"id": 6, "tokens": ["Professor", "Ada", "Liu", "presented", "her", "research", "at", "the", "conference", "in", "Tokyo", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.4, "duplication": 0.6}, "quality_score": 0.72}
{"id": 97, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "announced", "the", "launch", "of", "SolarFuture", "Innovations", "in", "Berlin", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9846, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.5882, "duplication": 0.4118}, "quality_score": 0.6918}
{"id": 69, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Jane", "Smith", "presented", "the", "new", "quantum", "algorithm", "at", "the", "conference", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9692, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.5882, "duplication": 0.4118}, "quality_score": 0.6872}
{"id": 21, "tokens": ["Ada", "Lovelace", "discussed", "quantum", "computing", "breakthroughs", "at", "the", "conference", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.2727, "duplication": 0.7273}, "quality_score": 0.6818}
{"id": 72, "tokens": ["Ada", "Lovelace", "discussed", "quantum", "computing", "at", "a", "conference", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.2727, "duplication": 0.7273}, "quality_score": 0.6818}
{"id": 52, "tokens": ["The", "headquarters", "of", "GlobalTech", "Industries", "opened", "a", "new", "office", "in", "Tokyo", "last", "month", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.25, "duplication": 0.75}, "quality_score": 0.675}
{"id": 57, "tokens": ["The", "headquarters", "of", "TechNova", "Solutions", "opened", "a", "new", "office", "in", "Barcelona", "last", "week", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.25, "duplication": 0.75}, "quality_score": 0.675}
{"id": 63, "tokens": ["The", "headquarters", "of", "GlobalTech", "Industries", "opened", "a", "new", "branch", "in", "Tokyo", "last", "week", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.25, "duplication": 0.75}, "quality_score": 0.675}
{"id": 77, "tokens": ["The", "headquarters", "of", "GlobalTech", "Solutions", "opened", "a", "new", "office", "in", "Tokyo", "last", "week", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.25, "duplication": 0.75}, "quality_score": 0.675}
{"id": 99, "tokens": ["The", "headquarters", "of", "GlobalTech", "Solutions", "opened", "a", "new", "branch", "in", "Tokyo", "last", "month", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.25, "duplication": 0.75}, "quality_score": 0.675}
{"id": 16, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "the", "new", "AI", "model", "at", "TechNova", "headquarters", "in", "Tokyo", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9867, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.4706, "duplication": 0.5294}, "quality_score": 0.6572}
{"id": 0, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "announced", "a", "partnership", "between", "Solaris", "Energy", "and", "local", "schools", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9857, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.4706, "duplication": 0.5294}, "quality_score": 0.6569}
{"id": 42, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Maria", "Alvarez", "announced", "a", "partnership", "between", "GlobalTech", "Industries", "and", "local", "universities", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9857, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.4706, "duplication": 0.5294}, "quality_score": 0.6569}
{"id": 46, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "announced", "the", "partnership", "between", "GlobalTech", "Solutions", "and", "local", "universities", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9857, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.4706, "duplication": 0.5294}, "quality_score": 0.6569}
{"id": 91, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "joined", "GlobalTech", "Innovations", "as", "chief", "scientist", "in", "Berlin", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9846, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.4375, "duplication": 0.5625}, "quality_score": 0.6466}
{"id": 86, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "joined", "the", "board", "of", "Global", "Health", "Initiative", "in", "Geneva", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9857, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.4211, "duplication": 0.5789}, "quality_score": 0.642}
{"id": 40, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "her", "breakthrough", "at", "the", "International", "Quantum", "Summit", "yesterday", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9857, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.4118, "duplication": 0.5882}, "quality_score": 0.6392}
{"id": 98, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "her", "research", "at", "the", "annual", "conference", "hosted", "by", "GlobalTech", "Innovations", "in", "Zurich", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9889, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.381, "duplication": 0.619}, "quality_score": 0.631}
{"id": 74, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "joined", "Global", "Health", "Initiative", "to", "expand", "services", "in", "Nairobi", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9857, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.375, "duplication": 0.625}, "quality_score": 0.6282}
{"id": 25, "tokens": ["Ada", "Lovelace", "gave", "a", "lecture", "in", "Cambridge", "about", "early", "computing", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.0833, "duplication": 0.9167}, "quality_score": 0.625}
{"id": 43, "tokens": ["Ada", "Lovelace", "gave", "a", "lecture", "in", "Cambridge", "about", "early", "computing", "breakthroughs", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.0833, "duplication": 0.9167}, "quality_score": 0.625}
{"id": 45, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Maria", "Gonzales", "presented", "a", "breakthrough", "at", "Global", "Health", "Institute", "in", "Berlin", "yesterday", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9867, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.3529, "duplication": 0.6471}, "quality_score": 0.6219}
{"id": 60, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "her", "findings", "at", "the", "global", "summit", "on", "renewable", "energy", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9867, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.3529, "duplication": 0.6471}, "quality_score": 0.6219}
{"id": 64, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "joined", "Global", "Health", "Initiative", "to", "combat", "malaria", "in", "Kenya", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9857, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.3333, "duplication": 0.6667}, "quality_score": 0.6157}
{"id": 17, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "joined", "Global", "Health", "Initiative", "to", "combat", "epidemics", "worldwide", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9846, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.3333, "duplication": 0.6667}, "quality_score": 0.6154}
{"id": 20, "tokens": ["The", "research", "team", "from", "GlobalTech", "Innovations", "presented", "their", "findings", "in", "Zurich", "conference", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.0, "duplication": 1.0}, "quality_score": 0.6}
{"id": 29, "tokens": ["The", "research", "team", "from", "GlobalTech", "Innovations", "presented", "their", "findings", "in", "Zurich", "conference", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.0, "duplication": 1.0}, "quality_score": 0.6}
{"id": 56, "tokens": ["The", "headquarters", "of", "GlobalTech", "Solutions", "opened", "a", "new", "office", "in", "Berlin", "last", "month", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.0, "duplication": 1.0}, "quality_score": 0.6}
{"id": 83, "tokens": ["The", "headquarters", "of", "GlobalTech", "Solutions", "opened", "a", "new", "office", "in", "Berlin", "last", "month", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 1.0, "label_consistency": 1.0, "diversity": 0.0, "duplication": 1.0}, "quality_score": 0.6}
{"id": 27, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "Global", "Health", "Initiative", "findings", "in", "Nairobi", "during", "the", "conference", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9867, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.2667, "duplication": 0.7333}, "quality_score": 0.596}
{"id": 65, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "her", "findings", "at", "the", "Global", "Tech", "Expo", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9846, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.2667, "duplication": 0.7333}, "quality_score": 0.5954}
{"id": 8, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "her", "findings", "at", "the", "Quantum", "Computing", "Summit", "in", "Berlin", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9867, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.25, "duplication": 0.75}, "quality_score": 0.591}
{"id": 44, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "her", "breakthrough", "at", "the", "Global", "Tech", "Expo", "in", "Berlin", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9867, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.25, "duplication": 0.75}, "quality_score": 0.591}
{"id": 94, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "her", "findings", "at", "the", "Global", "Tech", "Summit", "in", "Berlin", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9867, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.25, "duplication": 0.75}, "quality_score": 0.591}
{"id": 47, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "her", "research", "at", "Global", "Health", "Institute", "in", "Berlin", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9857, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.25, "duplication": 0.75}, "quality_score": 0.5907}
{"id": 22, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "her", "research", "at", "the", "Global", "Health", "Initiative", "conference", "in", "Berlin", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9875, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.2, "duplication": 0.8}, "quality_score": 0.5763}
{"id": 54, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "her", "findings", "at", "the", "global", "health", "summit", "in", "Geneva", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9867, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.2, "duplication": 0.8}, "quality_score": 0.576}
{"id": 84, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "a", "breakthrough", "at", "Global", "Health", "Institute", "in", "Nairobi", "yesterday", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9867, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.2, "duplication": 0.8}, "quality_score": 0.576}
{"id": 93, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "at", "the", "World", "Health", "Summit", "in", "Geneva", "last", "week", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9867, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.2, "duplication": 0.8}, "quality_score": 0.576}
{"id": 10, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "at", "Global", "Health", "Summit", "in", "Zurich", "last", "week", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9857, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.1538, "duplication": 0.8462}, "quality_score": 0.5618}
{"id": 92, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "her", "research", "at", "the", "conference", "in", "Berlin", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9846, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.1538, "duplication": 0.8462}, "quality_score": 0.5615}
{"id": 96, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "Global", "Health", "Initiative", "findings", "in", "Zurich", "conference", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9846, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.1538, "duplication": 0.8462}, "quality_score": 0.5615}
{"id": 59, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "joined", "Global", "Health", "Initiative", "as", "chief", "researcher", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9833, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.1538, "duplication": 0.8462}, "quality_score": 0.5611}
{"id": 85, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "at", "Global", "Health", "Summit", "in", "Zurich", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9833, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.1538, "duplication": 0.8462}, "quality_score": 0.5611}
{"id": 2, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "at", "the", "World", "Health", "Summit", "in", "Geneva", "yesterday", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9857, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.1429, "duplication": 0.8571}, "quality_score": 0.5586}
{"id": 12, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "a", "breakthrough", "at", "Global", "Health", "Institute", "in", "Geneva", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9857, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.1429, "duplication": 0.8571}, "quality_score": 0.5586}
{"id": 31, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "her", "research", "at", "the", "conference", "in", "Cairo", "yesterday", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9857, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.1429, "duplication": 0.8571}, "quality_score": 0.5586}
{"id": 67, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "a", "breakthrough", "at", "Global", "Health", "Initiative", "in", "Zurich", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9857, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.1429, "duplication": 0.8571}, "quality_score": 0.5586}
{"id": 78, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "a", "breakthrough", "at", "Global", "Health", "Institute", "in", "Zurich", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9857, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.1429, "duplication": 0.8571}, "quality_score": 0.5586}
{"id": 79, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "at", "the", "Global", "Health", "Summit", "in", "Geneva", "yesterday", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9857, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.1429, "duplication": 0.8571}, "quality_score": 0.5586}
{"id": 81, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "joined", "Global", "Health", "Initiative", "as", "chief", "researcher", "in", "Berlin", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9857, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.1429, "duplication": 0.8571}, "quality_score": 0.5586}
{"id": 35, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "her", "findings", "at", "the", "International", "Climate", "Summit", "in", "Geneva", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9867, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.1333, "duplication": 0.8667}, "quality_score": 0.556}
{"id": 15, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "her", "research", "at", "the", "annual", "conference", "of", "Global", "Health", "Initiative", "in", "Geneva", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9889, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.1111, "duplication": 0.8889}, "quality_score": 0.55}
{"id": 89, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "her", "research", "at", "the", "annual", "conference", "of", "Global", "Health", "Initiative", "in", "Zurich", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9889, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.1111, "duplication": 0.8889}, "quality_score": 0.55}
{"id": 26, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "her", "findings", "at", "the", "International", "Climate", "Summit", "in", "Berlin", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9867, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.0, "duplication": 1.0}, "quality_score": 0.516}
{"id": 76, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "her", "findings", "at", "the", "International", "Climate", "Summit", "in", "Berlin", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9867, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.0, "duplication": 1.0}, "quality_score": 0.516}
{"id": 7, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "joined", "Global", "Health", "Initiative", "as", "chief", "researcher", "in", "Nairobi", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9857, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.0, "duplication": 1.0}, "quality_score": 0.5157}
{"id": 11, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "at", "the", "Global", "Health", "Summit", "in", "Zurich", "yesterday", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9857, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.0, "duplication": 1.0}, "quality_score": 0.5157}
{"id": 19, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "her", "research", "at", "the", "conference", "in", "Tokyo", "yesterday", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9857, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.0, "duplication": 1.0}, "quality_score": 0.5157}
{"id": 28, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "her", "research", "at", "the", "conference", "in", "Tokyo", "yesterday", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9857, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.0, "duplication": 1.0}, "quality_score": 0.5157}
{"id": 58, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "at", "the", "Global", "Health", "Summit", "in", "Zurich", "yesterday", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9857, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.0, "duplication": 1.0}, "quality_score": 0.5157}
{"id": 61, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "joined", "Global", "Health", "Initiative", "as", "chief", "researcher", "in", "Nairobi", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9857, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.0, "duplication": 1.0}, "quality_score": 0.5157}
{"id": 70, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "at", "the", "Global", "Health", "Summit", "in", "Zurich", "yesterday", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9857, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.0, "duplication": 1.0}, "quality_score": 0.5157}
{"id": 1, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "her", "research", "at", "the", "conference", "in", "Tokyo", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9846, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.0, "duplication": 1.0}, "quality_score": 0.5154}
{"id": 30, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "Global", "Health", "Initiative", "findings", "in", "Tokyo", "conference", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9846, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.0, "duplication": 1.0}, "quality_score": 0.5154}
{"id": 36, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "her", "research", "at", "the", "conference", "in", "Tokyo", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9846, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.0, "duplication": 1.0}, "quality_score": 0.5154}
{"id": 37, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "her", "research", "at", "the", "conference", "in", "Tokyo", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9846, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.0, "duplication": 1.0}, "quality_score": 0.5154}
{"id": 53, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "her", "research", "at", "the", "conference", "in", "Tokyo", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9846, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.0, "duplication": 1.0}, "quality_score": 0.5154}
{"id": 55, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "her", "research", "at", "the", "conference", "in", "Tokyo", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9846, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.0, "duplication": 1.0}, "quality_score": 0.5154}
{"id": 62, "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Aisha", "Khan", "presented", "Global", "Health", "Initiative", "findings", "in", "Tokyo", "conference", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "quality_components": {"fluency": 0.9846, "label_consistency": 0.8, "diversity": 0.0, "duplication": 1.0}, "quality_score": 0.5154}
